{
  "question": [{
    "questionText": "whats kostas name",
    "realAnswer": "kosta"
  }, {
    "questionText": "whats nadavs name",
    "realAnswer": "nadav"
  }, {
    "questionText": "who you gonna call",
    "realAnswer": "ghost busters"
  }, {
    "questionText": "what is love",
    "realAnswer": "baby dont hurt me"
  }, {
    "questionText": "who was right",
    "realAnswer": "kahana"
  }, {
    "questionText": "___, i did it again",
    "realAnswer": "oops"
  }, {
    "questionText": "what did the zebra wear on tuesday",
    "realAnswer": "sports suit"
  }, {
    "questionText": "what time is it in zimbabweh",
    "realAnswer": "who cares"
  }, {
    "questionText": "whos the boss",
    "realAnswer": "mona"
  }, {
    "questionText": "whos the best friend",
    "realAnswer": "joey"
  }, {
    "questionText": "____ wait for it... -dary",
    "realAnswer": "legen"
  }, {
    "questionText": "liron or roslana",
    "realAnswer": "liron"
  }, {
    "questionText": "___ you guys in going home",
    "realAnswer": "screw"
  }, {
    "questionText": "Kyle's mom is a big fat ____",
    "realAnswer": "bitch"
  }, {
    "questionText": "I'm ______",
    "realAnswer": "batman"
  }, {
    "questionText": "who is the pumpkin king?",
    "realAnswer": "jack"
  }, {
    "questionText": "there's a lady who's sure all that glitters is ____",
    "realAnswer": "gold"
  }]
}
